(dramatic orchestral music)
(dramatic orchestral
music continues)
(wings fluttering)
(dramatic orchestral
music continues)
(bow clicking)
(arrow thudding)
- (bow clicking)
- (arrow thudding)
What's the point of shooting
if you're not gonna
read the conditions?
- (bow clicking)
- (arrow thudding)
It's mindless.
Look, it's 10 knots northerly.
The conditions at the flag...
The conditions of the flag
do not represent the conditions
of the target.
Yes, I know.
Right. So if you understand it,
make your adjustments.
(cow mooing)
(woman) Block it.
Okay, now feel the wind.
Look for a pattern.
- Ten knots.
- (wind blowing)
Twelve knots.
- (bike clicking)
- Fifteen.
Just feel it.
Don't you have
anything better to do?
If you can't take the feedback,
how are you gonna improve?
(arrow thudding)
Sharp shooting!
Kids, you're late for school.
Go on. Don't forget tomorrow
we're doing lunch here.
I'm gonna cook up
a feed for her birthday.
Oh, you don't have to do that.
I'm 16, not five.
Remember?
I'd be keen to come along,
no matter what she says
about your cooking.
School.
Okay. See ya.
(engine revving)
- You okay?
- Yeah.
She just sucks.
(chuckling) I assume
you didn't tell her
about tonight, then.
Shit no,
that's tomorrow's problem.
(boy) Good point.
(engine rumbling)
(tense music)
(door clicking)
(engine revving)
(tense music continues)
G'day there.
Mrs. Kris Hendricks, right?
(tense music continues)
Peter Phillips.
That was
a high-stress situation.
You didn't flinch.
They told me you'd do that.
They all flinched.
I represent foreign interests,
corporate farmers.
(laughing) What company is that?
(chuckling) Well, come on now.
That would be pillow talk,
wouldn't it?
Look at this.
A hundred and thirty hectares
at three and a half per.
That gives you 350,000
clear after debts.
It's a fresh start, Kris.
It's not for sale, mate.
Everything has a price.
Watch out for the cow shit.
(tense music continues)
(door clicking)
(bag unzipping)
(tense music continues)
(engine revving)
- (gun firing)
- (tire blowing)
(car crashing)
(gun cocking)
You've got 10 seconds to tell me
who you are, Mr. Phillips.
Seven seconds.
Five seconds.
And another one for the bullet
to pass through your body.
Who are you?!
(tense music intensifying)
(gun firing)
(engine starting)
(engine revving)
(gun firing)
(car crunching)
(tense music continues)
(door thudding)
(phone ringing)
(ringing stops)
(Phillips grunting)
Fuck, fuck, fuck...
(phone beeping)
(Phillips sighs)
(gun clicking)
He's coming.
Voodoo Child.
(gasping)
Long live The Dragon.
(gun firing)
(tense music)
(door clicking)
(gas splashing)
(match striking)
(fire whooshing)
(line ringing)
(receptionist)
Hello, Barren Back High School.
Oh, hi.
This is Kris Hendricks,
Anja's mother.
- (receptionist) Mrs. Hendricks.
- Listen,
there's been a family emergency,
so I'm gonna be
coming in early today.
(receptionist) Oh, well,
that will be tricky.
Anja hasn't been to school
for almost two weeks now.
And we have tried,
but you are very difficult--
(tense music)
(door clicking)
(Kris) Where are you?
(tense music continues)
- (Kris) It's me.
- (man) Voodoo.
- It's me, okay?
- Been a long time.
- Missed you.
- Yeah, missed you too.
(man) Situation?
He's alive.
100%.
(man) You're sure?
(Kris) I just buried
one of his men.
He said,
"Long live The Dragon,"
just before I put
a bullet in his head.
(man) Sixteen years,
you're still chasing ghosts.
It could be some lunatic
chasing an old bounty,
trading on The Dragon's name.
(Kris) On my life, Dog,
it's him.
(Dog sighing) What do you need?
(Kris) Ex-snipers, our team.
As many as you can get.
(Dog) Oh,
that's a hell of an ask.
Kris, half the team's gone.
Some won't fight again,
some can't.
You've been
off the grid a long time.
(Kris) Make it work.
I'll send coordinates.
There's a marked-up map
of the property.
Now, he'll come
under the cover of dark.
Maybe tonight
if he's moved straight away.
(Dog) Fine.
I'll be there, but hear me.
If this really is a ghost hunt,
it's gonna cost you big time.
- (tense music)
- (line ringing)
Hey, it's Anja.
Sorry I can't take your call.
I'm not actually ignoring you--
(line ringing)
Hello, it's Michael.
Sorry I can't get to the phone.
(engine revving)
(Kris)
Anja, I need you to call me.
I know you haven't been
at school.
I don't care
about that right now.
I just need you to call me
and tell me where you are.
(line ringing)
Michael, are you with Anja?
Please, I need Anja to call me.
Just come home.
- It's urgent.
- (door clicking)
Anja!
Okay.
Fuck off.
(laughing)
(line ringing)
(Kris) Hi, Jen.
It's Kris.
Um, listen, do you know
if the kids are together?
I'm really just trying
to get hold of Anja.
Yeah, so if you hear anything,
can you gimme a call?
Thanks.
- (lights clicking)
- (tense music)
I'm not gonna marry you, though.
Yeah, I didn't think you would.
I'm not taking it off, though.
I didn't think you would.
(both laughing)
(tense music)
(insects chirring)
(gun clicking)
(helicopter whirring)
Almost as good as this.
(laughing)
(tense music)
Come on.
We're going
for lunch later anyway.
A chopper buzzed
our heads, Michael.
It's probably just roo shooters.
(Anja) I wanna know
what's going on.
(tense music)
(Michael) Just stay here.
- I'll be right back.
- It's your birthday.
(engine revving)
(tense music)
(gun firing)
- (gun firing)
- (Michael grunting)
(egg sizzling)
(birds squawking)
(tense music)
(helicopter whirring)
I love what you've done
with the place, Voodoo.
How's the nightlife? (chuckling)
Where's Angelo?
Guatemala or Colombia.
Retired to the drug trade
or got married.
I can't remember which.
Where's Dokic?
He's a chef in Perth.
Who do you think I am?
ASIS, the CIA, the UN?
- This is it.
- Nine ex-snipers
with time on the ground.
Sixteen years ago
it was nine snipers.
Now all that's left
is a reputation.
Look, you needed ex-soldiers
who were within range
of getting here ASAP.
This is Australia, isn't it?
Not exactly around the corner
for the rest of the world.
Now make it worth it, will you?
Besides that chopper
cost me 20K.
I'll cover it.
Yeah, I can see
you've done real well
for yourself out here, soldier.
(sighing) Jeez, you must
be pretty fucking certain
it's not The Dragon or you
wouldn't have brought him along.
He's trained. He'll stay back.
I wanted to come.
New security job isn't quite
hitting the same.
Nothing wrong with security.
Face of an angel,
just like his dad.
(both laughing)
Kris Hendricks.
No relation to Jimi...
Hendrix, yeah.
Over there is,
on the crest, is Milk.
(Dog) I'm sure you have
no trouble recognizing him
from the old unit.
And over there is Kalda.
She's ex-KFOR, possibly Italian.
Who knows? Doesn't say much.
And this is Nico.
We did some good in Afghanistan
and now he...
he contracts for me.
All ex-military. All good to go.
Voodoo Child, like the song.
(tense music)
(Dog) Hey, Nico.
You did not say this mission
involved Voodoo Child.
I said it's a security detail,
serve and protect.
- It's The Dragon.
- The Dragon's dead.
I don't go up against
The Dragon for a favor.
She needs to be paranoid.
Well, of course
she needs to be paranoid.
There's a 10 million bounty
on her fucking head.
I might as well
take her out myself.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
This is a death watch.
We've seen enough of them.
There wasn't time
for full disclosure.
You didn't ask questions.
I was doing you a favor, mate.
Nico.
Nico!
Is that true?
The Dragon's dead, Junior.
(tense music continues)
(engine rumbling)
(door creaking)
He was calling himself
Phillips, real estate agent.
He had a bloody business card
and everything.
That's north?
He sent off a message
via his cell phone.
Trashed it before he died.
Oh, 10 million
attracts a lot of crazies.
Even if there's
no one left to pay it.
Soon enough one of us
is gonna be dead.
Then we'll know
The Dragon has arrived.
(tense music)
(door creaking)
(speaking Italian)
Yeah, well, um,
I'm a little bit rusty.
I did spend some time
in the south.
Where are you from?
Sydney.
You do understand
who's out there, don't you?
I understand that
I'm here to protect
a mother and her kid.
- (door creaking)
- (tense music)
(engine rumbling)
(Anja) Why is this here?
(engine revving)
(tense music continues)
(Kalda) Contact, 700 meters
slight right of my access.
Target moving left to the right
in the tree line.
Clear to engage?
(tense music continues)
(Kris) It's her.
- It's her.
- Okay, we got a 15-year-old
still out there somewhere.
Do not engage until
subject is verified, roger?
She's 16.
It's her birthday.
(Dog) Good hunting, KD.
Cover the front, Junior.
Hold your fire.
- She's a friendly, confirm?
- (snipers) Copy.
I'm gonna put one in the tree.
Make her get down.
- Relay?
- (Dog) Hold positions, hold.
Probing fire from my position.
Say again.
Probing fire only. Send it.
(gun firing)
Get down.
(shaky breathing)
Go on, get down.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
Oh, shit!
She's been hit.
Shot fired.
(Dog) Report, shot fired, identify.
(Kris) Where's that shot from?
(man) Anja? Anja?
- Yeah?
- (Anja) Mmm.
I'm Nico.
That was your mom
telling you to stay down.
There's gonna be somebody
over there who's gonna come here
and grab you,
but you've gotta stay low.
- Yeah?
- Okay.
This is a bad place now.
It's not somewhere
for you to be.
Just stick by your mom
no matter what you see.
Okay.
Stay here.
(tense music)
(Nico) Anja's safe.
She's unharmed
and waiting for retrieval.
Anja?
(Anja) Mom, what's happening?
Hey.
I won't go.
Hide that shit.
All right?
Now, get it together, girl.
Let's go.
(tense music)
- (Dog) Friendly's incoming.
- (Junior) Copy.
All right, so this is Malcolm.
People call him White Dog.
That's Junior, he's my son.
We've got a situation.
There's a boy out there alone.
I'm gonna have to go get him.
Mom, what... what's going on?
Put some clothes on. Stay low.
Ah, just hold there, fella.
(Junior) Dad, just relax.
Fucking hell.
Okay, you all right?
So...
There's a man out there
looking for revenge
for something that happened
a long time ago.
These people are here to help.
They're from the Army.
They don't look like medics.
You weren't a medic, were you?
I have medical training.
Okay, you're gonna have to
tell me where you've been hiding
when you've been
skipping school.
The western edge
near the Sullivan's boundary.
Oh, shit.
(Anja) I want to come.
I have to get to Michael.
No, you stay here. You're safe.
I will trust these people
with your life.
- (gun firing)
- (low tense music)
(Junior, muted) Dad!
(tense music continues)
(Kris, normal volume) White Dog
is dead.
Kal, get to the house now.
- (tense music continues)
- (bird squawking)
- (footsteps thudding)
- (Anja breathing shakily)
(Kalda) You need to
get out of here right now.
(Anja) What about Michael?
(Milk) It's Milk.
I'm in position.
(Kris) Copy that.
We need to draw him out
before he moves.
I can use the head wound
to figure out
The Dragon's position.
(Kalda) Yep.
(flesh squelching)
(Kris) It's not a 50.
It's a 7.62 NATO.
Range around 600 meters.
(flesh squelching)
- (Kris grunts)
- (flesh squelching)
- (Kris grunting)
- Stop.
(Kris grunting)
(Kris) It's too compromised.
It's not gonna work.
All right, we'll use him
as a target. (grunting)
See if we can draw fire.
Come on, come on.
(gun firing)
(Kris screaming) No!
- (breathing shakily)
- (Kris) Anja, stay down.
(tense music)
(Kris) Milk, Kal's been hit.
(tense music continues)
Where's your girl?
In her room.
(engine revving)
- (Kris) Milk's AC.
- Where are you going?
Where are you going?
(tense music)
(engine rumbling)
(engine revving)
No. No, no, no, no, no.
No...
Mom, we have to call someone.
We have to call someone.
- We will.
- No, no.
We will.
The dingoes
will get him out here.
We have to make sure that
he's safe, Mom. (sobbing)
- This isn't okay.
- We're gonna stay with him.
(sobbing) No, no.
We're gonna stay
with him tonight, all right?
(sobbing)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(Anja sobbing)
(crickets chirping)
- (gun firing)
- (glass shattering)
(ominous music)
(gun firing)
(Milk) Junior.
Junior, kill the light.
(ominous music continues)
(phone beeping)
Stevie, it's Junior.
We need immediate evac
from the drop point.
Dragon's here and
he's dropping bodies.
No.
No, no. No, no. What do
you mean, "call the cops"?
Dad is dead.
Kaldayev's dead.
Immediate fucking evac!
(ominous music continues)
0700 hours, roger.
(breathing heavily)
Should we call the cops?
Why don't you just...
keep your head down?
See if we can't get
through the night, hey?
(Anja) Are we even safe here?
(Kris) It's too dark to move.
We'll wait till first light.
I don't know you at all, do I?
Well, that's not true.
Have you killed a lot of people?
You knew I was a soldier.
How many?
Or are you not allowed
to talk about it?
You know, you're just...
too fucking traumatized
or something?
How many?
Hundred and sixteen.
Verified.
Does that include, um,
does that include Michael?
This is what he'd want.
You, me, Michael like this.
Yeah, he'd be figuring
that the trauma
of spending the night out here
with a loved one will compromise
my psychological readiness.
(dramatic orchestral music)
First you survive.
Then you've gotta
live with yourself.
Except you disappeared.
I called you so many times.
The PX tent, Private Milk.
He said you were deployed,
but I knew he was lying.
I kept calling, one week, two.
I kept calling every single day.
Plus 96-444-5938-0025.
RAR, Private Milk, Anja?
Milk would always
read me bedtime stories.
You never did that.
(dramatic orchestral music
continues)
(birds chirping)
- (helicopter whirring)
- (tense music)
Mom, what's happening?
(Kris) Could be a friendly.
(tense music continues)
(gun firing)
- (helicopter crashing)
- Run, get back to the house.
(tense music continues)
(engine revving)
(gun firing)
(tense music continues)
(screaming)
(gun firing)
(Milk) You can't escape him.
You're safer in here with me
than out there, trust me.
In case you get close.
I'm sorry.
(Junior breathing heavily)
(tense music)
(tense music continues)
(Kris panting)
Damn you, Dragon.
(tense music continues)
(menacing music)
(Dragon) Up you get.
You know, you should have
seen me coming. Right?
I made it this far.
Yeah. Yeah, you did.
Why are you doing this?
(Dragon) To claim what's mine.
She's not like us.
Yeah, she is.
Please...
Please just leave her.
No.
One by one, I'll take
the rest of your team down
and when I kill you, I'll take
her home where she belongs
and make her forget
you ever existed.
You know the game.
This bandana.
Shot for shot.
All right.
(gun clicking)
(tense music)
Two is one and one is none.
(tense music continues)
(Kris breathing heavily)
(breathing heavily)
(gun firing)
(grunting)
Oh, fuck.
(tense music)
Oh, shit.
(tense music continues)
Wait, wait, Junior.
(gun firing)
Shit.
(footsteps thudding)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(dramatic orchestral
music continues)
(breathing heavily)
Fuck!
We gotta move.
He fucking shot me.
(tense music)
(Junior pants) Oh, fuck.
Show me. Show me. Where?
Am I gonna die?
- Maybe.
- Oh, shit.
I never wanted to come here.
Oh, fuck.
All right, we gotta go.
I wanna get you
back to the house.
Fuck.
We're gonna go six o'clock
west backwards.
Okay, you ready?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
- Okay. Yeah.
- Come on. Come on!
Six o'clock, 500,
then west up the hill.
- Okay?
- I can't.
Junior, you fucking move!
Fucking move now!
- (gun firing)
- (Junior yells)
Oh, Jesus, we gotta get moving.
We gotta get outta here,
or we're gonna die.
Don't leave me, please.
We're gonna die.
(tense music continues)
(Junior breathing heavily)
Voodoo, it's Nico.
On your six, hold your position.
(tense music continues)
(Nico exhaling deeply)
(gun firing)
(gun cocking)
(Junior panting)
Don't tell my dad.
I won't.
I've never shot anyone.
That's good.
I just bought a dog.
(soft tense music)
Did you hit him?
I missed, he's on the move.
(soft tense music continues)
(panting)
Is he...
What is it? Three kilometers?
We can make it.
(soft tense music continues)
(Junior grunting)
(tense music intensifies)
- (Nico) Stay put.
- (Kris) Okay.
Put him down, get him down.
Get down.
(Nico grunting)
(tense music continues)
(gun firing)
(gun cocking)
- Nico!
- (gun firing)
(somber music)
(Junior breathing heavily)
(phone beeping)
It's encrypted.
You're gonna wanna eat that.
You'll need your energy.
It's gonna be a long day.
♪ Incy wincy spider
Went up the waterspout ♪
Private Milk!
(Milk laughing) Yes.
Private Milk.
I saw something amazing once.
Your mom... in Iraq.
Two psychopaths
on the back of a motorbike
with a chest full of plastic.
Explosives.
They were screaming
and coming towards us
and everyone's
shooting and missing.
But your mom, she took
her time to change her ammo
to an armor-piercing round.
Boom. Two kills, one shot.
Never seen anything like it.
(Junior groaning)
(Milk) In all that chaos,
your mom...
she just took her time.
(both grunting)
We spoke about you a lot
when we were in camp.
My boyfriend is dead, Milk.
He's out there
alone under a tree.
(Kris) Milk!
- I need your help here.
- Coming.
(all grunting)
Okay. There you go,
come on, we've got you.
Yes, that's it.
(Milk) There you go, mate.
- Okay, got it.
- (Junior groaning)
(Kris) This is a lot of blood.
I'll get something for the pain.
(Kris) We made it back, mate.
You're gonna be all right.
(tense music)
(gas splashing)
(Milk) I'm gonna try
and clean this,
and then I'll need you
to apply pressure.
Okay?
Jesus, he's made a hell of
a mess of your six-pack,
hasn't he, mate?
We should get on the move.
Keep Anja safe.
She is safe.
You spoke to him.
And he let you live?
(tense music continues)
(Junior groaning)
(both grunting)
(Junior exhaling softly)
(tense music continues)
All is well. All is well.
All is well. There's only good
that will come.
We're all safe, we're all safe.
(tense music continues)
I know why.
(tank rumbling)
(ominous music)
(ominous sting)
(Anja) You said I'm safe.
I know why.
- (Milk) Anja, Anja.
- I'm gonna get help.
Anja, Anja!
- (gun firing)
- (Kris) No!
- (Anja gasping)
(gun firing)
He's not gonna hurt her
until he has no choice.
Fuck it, I'm going.
- Milk!
- (Milk grunting)
(gun cocking)
(tense music continues)
She's safe...
because she's his daughter.
(Kris) You remember that UN
mission in the Sar Mountains
16 years ago,
when my team was ambushed
and captured by rebels?
Well, The Dragon
was their warlord.
The men in our team
were executed.
The women were kept alive.
When The Dragon
found out who I was...
(gun firing)
...forced me into his duels.
Red bandana, shot for shot.
Win, you live,
lose, you die.
When the time came,
I executed a plan.
(explosion booming)
Compound was bombed.
I got out alive,
but I carried
a piece of him with me.
Anja.
He's come to take her home.
Well, okay then.
Then you better go to her.
He's too good.
Under 700, he's too good.
I've got his number.
I'll find him
and I'll shoot him...
or he'll shoot me.
You're her mother.
Don't you dare let her go.
When I'm done...
light it up.
(suspenseful music)
(gun firing)
(engine revving)
Jesus.
For fuck's sakes, get in!
Anja!
(suspenseful music continues)
Get in!
(gun firing)
(Anja panting)
Stay down.
(panting)
- (gun firing)
- (Kris grunting)
Mom, are you okay? Mom?
I'm okay.
Anja, stay down.
- Stay down.
- Where's Milk?
(suspenseful music continues)
(Kris) Milk, The Dragon's here.
(match striking)
(fire whooshing)
(screaming) Milk!
(Kris) Stop, Anja!
He's safe, he's safe!
(intense suspenseful music)
(gun firing)
(intense suspenseful music
continues)
(door creaking)
(gun firing)
- (gun firing)
- (Milk grunting)
(groaning)
(gun firing)
(screaming)
- (arrow thudding)
- (Dragon grunting)
(tense music)
(Milk breathing heavily)
(Milk) Anja.
(Dragon grunting)
- (gun firing)
- (grunts)
(laughing)
(grunting)
(gun firing)
(groaning)
Anja.
(tense music)
(Dragon) Oi.
Let him go.
Let Milk live.
You have no idea
what you are, do you?
All right, one can live.
Your Milk or your mom.
You get to choose.
All right?
(footsteps thudding)
(groaning)
Get up, get up.
Put your fucking gun down.
- (tense music continues)
- (Dragon) Thank you.
Here.
Here you go.
Give this to your mom.
She knows what comes next.
(thunder rumbling)
(tense music continues)
(grunting)
(Anja grunting)
(Milk breathing heavily)
(tense music intensifies)
(gun firing)
(tense music continues)
(Anja) Mom, what's happening?
We're gonna trade shots.
You've got no scope.
I've got you.
Take it.
(tense music)
Two is one.
One is none.
Together, we survive.
(tense music continues)
All right.
(Kris) Call it.
He's 950, maybe.
Uphill, maybe five meters.
Wind?
Um... nothing, maybe four knots.
(tense music continues)
(gun firing)
Um, you're two meters to
the left, and you're five short.
Okay.
(tense music continues)
Get behind the truck.
(gun firing)
(menacing music)
All right, give me the wind.
Um, five knots steady.
No, um, three.
Breathe.
Gusting five to three.
Okay, look for a pattern.
(thunder rumbling)
(tense music)
(rain pattering)
(Anja) Three knots.
Five. Five. Three. Five, five.
Two knots, five knots.
(tense music continues)
Three knots, five,
five, three, five knots,
three knots, five, five.
- (Kris) Three.
- (gun firing)
You missed! Mom, you missed.
(intense ominous music)
Mom, can you please just hide?
(ominous music continues)
Mom, he will kill you.
(inaudible)
(gun firing)
(bullet whooshing)
(gasping)
(soft tense music)
You hit him.
(Dragon grunting)
(gentle music)
(gasping, laughing)
(gentle music continues)
(dramatic music)
(dramatic music continues)
(gentle closing music)